SAMER SAMI

Position title

PROFILE

An employee can work hard alone and with colleagues to meet deadlines require and to build up a professional team in order to improve the productivity of the organization.

Although working in the same department will increase knowledge and experience in addition, working on different departments can increase knowledge and improve the ability of an employee.

+97336973881

makessmer89@gmail.com

Bahrain - Aali

22 years old





WORK EXPERIENCE

Cashier

Aswaq al Helli | Sep 2016 - Feb 2018

- 1. Receiving customers' applications and registering them on Cashier.
- 2. Make sure the accounts are properly settled last day.
- 3. Notify the supervisor if there is a customer that can not be served as is.
- 4. Transfer any feedback or suggestions from customers to the manager.
- customer service

Aswaq al Helli | Feb 2018 - present

- 1. Working in the interest of both the company and the client
- 2. The polite and respectful approach with customers
- 3. Work long-term relationships with customers
- 4. Good handling of customers' grievances
- 5. Providing a distinguished service to customers
- 6. Making requests and checking the missing goods in the shop

EDUCATION

scientific_discipline

Al taawon secondary school | Sept 2013 - May 2016 Biology is a natural science that means the study of life and living organisms, including their structures, functions, growth, evolution, distribution and classification

Chemistry is a science based on the study of materials and chemical elements and mutual relations between them and identify the composition of chemicals and changes that occur

marketing

University of Bahrain | June 2016 - present

Marketing specialization: The process by which goods are transferred from producers to consumers and the marketing method of the product to be sold.

Selling the product, announcing the price and talking about the product with all credibility and honesty to attract customers to buy the advertised products in the place allocated.

SKILLS

Professional

Microsoft office (word, excel).

Effectively in communicative.

Ability to work in team.

Ability to work under pressure and overtime.

Good organizer and Flexibility.

Maintaining emotional control under stress.

Multi-tasking and Quick learning skills.

Languages

ARABIC

ENGLISH

French

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Swimming
- fishing

AWARDS

Available upon request